Now looking at our list of tasks to do,
现在看看我们的任务列表
we could tackle them from the top to bottom.
我们可以从上往下处理每项任务
So remember in the last lesson I mentioned that there are a number of
在上一节课中 我提到你可以按照多种方式
ways that you can prioritize your tasks.
安排任务的优先级
So one way go about this is to try the hardest or
一种方式是首先尝试最难的或
riskiest tasks first making sure that that feature is even possible.
最冒险的任务 弄清楚该功能是否可行
Now for us, we've never played an audio file before, so
对我们来说 我们之前从来没播放过音频文件
let's just make sure that even works.
所以要先确定这一点是可行的
So, the lowest risk item on this list is adding the play button icon
这个列表中 风险最低的一项是向列表项中
to the list items and this is because we've modified layouts before so
添加播放按钮图标 因为我们之前已经修改过布局
we know that this is possible.
所以知道该任务是能够完成的
So, let's go ahead and save this UI change for
所以我们将这个 UI 更改任务留到课程结束时
the end of the lesson when we go ahead and do the visual polish.
到时候我们改善外观时会同时完成这项任务
To get started, we're going to have you create a tiny music player app
要开始 请先创建一个与 Miwok 应用
separate from the me walk app.
独立开来的小型音乐播放器应用
Developers often write a small app to test a new technology before building it
开发人员通常会写一个小应用 测试下新技术
into their own larger app.
然后将该技术添加到自己的大型应用中
Now by creating this sample app, you'll become familiar with
通过创建这个示例应用 你将熟悉
the MediaPlayer API, and by the way, you may hear the term API come up
MediaPlayer API 顺便提下 你可能偶尔听过
occasionally and that's just an acronym for application programming interface.
API 这个术语 它是应用程序接口的缩写
So when we talked about interfaces earlier,
我们之前讨论过接口
remember they're like contracts that Android provides promising certain
它们就像 Android 提供的一种合同
functionality, so things like playing media using the MediaPlayer class.
保证向我们提供某些功能 例如使用 MediaPlayer 类播放媒体
So we don't need to know all the details within the MediaPlayer class,
我们不需要知道 MediaPlayer 类中的所有细节
things like like how gets the sound to come out of the speakers on a device,
例如如何让设备上的扬声器发出声音
but as a developer, we just care that we can use the MediaPlayer and
作为开发人员 我们只关心我们可以使用 MediaPlayer
call methods on it to play media files.
并对其调用方法来播放媒体文件
Right, for this quiz,
对于这道测试题
you'll be building this simplified music player app that works for a single song.
你将构建一个简单的音乐播放器应用 可以播放一首歌曲
So in this app, hitting Play
在这个应用中 点按“播放”
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC]
plays a song and hitting Pause, pauses the song.
播放了一首歌曲 点按“暂停”音乐暂停了
Now when you hit Play again, it's going to resume where it was paused.
当你再次点按“播放”它会从暂停的位置继续播放
[MUSIC]
[音乐]
First create a new project in Android Studio and
首先在 Android Studio 中创建一个新项目
start with the empty activity template and go ahead and build out this layout.
使用空的 Activity 模板并构建出这个布局
In the notes below the quiz, we've provided a link to help find and
在测试题下方的备注中 我们提供了相关链接帮助你
download sample MP3 files for your app.
找到并下载示例 MP3 文件并用于你的应用
Note that you could also use your own MP3 files if you want.
注意 你也可以使用自己的 MP3 文件
Be sure that the audio file is stored in the raw folder
确保将音频文件存储在 raw 文件夹中
within the res directory of the app.
位于应用的 res 目录下
To create the raw folder, within the project structure tab of your app,
要创建该 raw 文件夹 在应用的项目结构标签页中
right-click on the res folder &gt; New &gt;
右击 res 文件夹 依次选择“新建 (New)”
Android resource directory, then name the new directory raw,
“Android 资源目录 (Android resource directory)”
r-a-a, and choose its resource type to be raw as well, and then hit OK.
然后将新目录命名为“raw”并将资源类型也选择为 raw 按“确定 (OK)”
Then you can copy and paste the song file into this raw folder.
然后将歌曲文件复制粘贴到这个 raw 文件夹中
Our MP3 file is a pre-encoded file that needs to be processed as is or raw.
我们的 MP3 文件是预编码的文件 需要按原样处理 即处理成原始内容
For a more detailed description on resource folders, check out
要详细了解资源文件夹
the providing resources article in the notes below the quiz and then we'd
请参阅测试题下方备注中提供的资源文章
like you to add the provided audio file to the res/raw directory of your app.
然后将提供的音频文件添加到应用的 res/raw 目录下
Then I'd like you to modify the code by adding on-click listeners
然后请修改代码 添加 OnClickListener
to make each of the buttons actually play and pause the song.
使每个按钮都能实际地播放和暂停歌曲
Also give it a try and
同时尝试使用下
experiment with other functionality provided by the MediaPlayer class.
MediaPlayer 类提供的其他功能
So for example, you can try adding a button that changes the volume or
例如 添加一个按钮来更改音量
even skips the middle of the song.
甚至跳到歌曲的中间部分
So for this task,
对于这项任务
you'll need to research how to use the MediaPlayer on Android.
你需要研究如何使用 Android 上的 MediaPlayer
To make this all work, we won't provide you the exact website to reference.
我们不会提供具体的参考网站
Instead, take a look at tutorials on MediaPlayer in Android on your own and
请你自己查看 Android 中关于 MediaPlayer 的教程
then do some trial and error on your app to make it work.
然后在你的应用上作出尝试 发现错误 并最终使应用能运行
So best of luck.
祝你好运